nationmultimedia.com 2004-06-04

# Welcome to The Nation

### Privacy Policy for www.NationMultiMedia.com

_www.nationmultimedia.com_ regards your online privacy as an important and serious matter. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to this issue. 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for _www.nationmultimedia.com._

As _www.nationmultimedia.com_ continues to develop we may add new features, change the type of information we gather or the method by which it is gathered. We will adjust this privacy policy to reflect any future changes, and notify users of any personal information we are requesting. Please review this policy for changes from time to time, and contact us if you have any questions. 

**TOPICS THIS STATEMENT COVERS**  
IP Addresses - Surveys - Children Cookies Contests Security Registration Third Party Advertising Order Forms Public Forums 

**IP ADDRESSES:** An IP address is a number assigned to the computer which is requesting a web page from our site. Usually it is not your personal computer, but a computer used by your internet service provider or company network. www.nationmultimedia.com uses IP addresses (of 209.50.230.79) to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to report aggregate information. 

**COOKIES:** A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

We use cookies to help target ads based on user behavior. For example, our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver more targeted advertising, such as ads based on your zip code. For more information on cookies, please see the section on third party web sites below. 

**SURVEYS:** Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis only. We may ask for contact information if we are providing an incentive to users for completing our surveys. The contact information is kept private and only used to contact you if necessary. It is kept separate from any demographic information you provide. If we plan to use this information for those purposes, we will notify users at the point at which we collect the information and allow users to opt-out of having their information used for those purposes. 

**CONTESTS:** We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary. This information is kept private. We currently do not use this information for marketing purposes or sell it to third parties. If we plan to use this information for those purposes, we will notify users at the point at which we collect the information and allow users to opt-out of having their information used for those purposes. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND CONTENT:** www.nationmultimedia.com has partnerships with other companies and links to other web sites, including but not limited to those listed herewith. If you choose to use the services provided by those sites, you may be asked by those sites to provide certain personally indentifiable information. Some of this information may, on an individual or aggregated basis, be shared with us. However, we will keep any individually identifiable information private. Please be aware that www.nationmultimedia.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites, even if our name or logo may appear on those sites. Third party web sites may appear in a new window, or they may appear in a frame. If frames are used, you may still see our site's URL in the address window, but you are actually on another web site. In most cases, any third party web page, even in a frame, is branded with their name. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. 

At the moment, www.nationmultimedia.com, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data about your visit to this and other web sites, typically through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>. 

**PUBLIC FORUMS:** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to our users. Some of these forums require registration. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**SECURITY:** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Any financial information provided by users is sent via a secure server and encrypted for user protection. 

**CONTACTING THE WEB SITE:** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

\-------------------

Nation Internet [info@nationmultimedia.com](mailto:info@nationmultimedia.com)  
(c)2000 Nation Multimedia Group  
44 Moo 10 Bang Na-Trat KM 4.5, Bang Na district, Bangkok 10260 Thailand   
Tel 66-2-325-5555 ext 2457 or fax 66-2-317-2071
